Guide to the William R. and Louise Fielder Sheet Music Collection
Department of Special Collections
- Series 6. California
  - Subseries a. Illustrated with original photographs
    - After the opera's over San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1872 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Arranged by Carl Hess
      Mr. J. H. Milburn's Musical Bouquet
    - The flower girl's gavotte à la schottische San Francisco: Matthias Gray Co.,1887 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Composed by J. Donigan
      Photographer Cha[rle]s Lainer, San Francisco
    - Little birdie sing and cheer me San Francisco: Sherman, Hyde & Co.,1876 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Music by Lillian
      Words by De Witt Hubbell
    - In the wide world (In die Weite Welt): marche des Amazones San Francisco: Sherman, Hyde & Co. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Music by Carl Faust
      Naiad Queen
    - Aladdin quadrille: Schotische San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Music by Carl Hess
    - Grand March of King Henry V San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1876 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Arranged by J. H. Dohrmann
    - Ten thousand miles away: the tread mill song San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1871 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Subseries b. 1836 - 1849, Westward Ho
    - The California quick step Philadelphia: E. Ferrett & Co.,1849 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The miner's quick step Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1849 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Composed by A. F. Holmes
    - The gold mines of California, or, Leonore grand march, in which is introduced Weigl's beautiful air of Leonore Boston: G. P. Reed & Co.,1849 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Composed and Arranged by Louis Strack
    - California quick step, introducing the popular air of Uncle Ned Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1849 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Arranged by Edward L. White
    - Pull away cheerily! the gold digger's song London: Musical Bouquet Office and J. Allen,n.d. (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Written by Harry Lee Carter
      Performed by Harry Lee Carter and George Henry Russell
    - Cheer, boys, cheer! London: Musical Bouquet Office and J. Allen,n.d. (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Words by Charles Mackay, L.L.D.
      The Emigrant's Progress, or, Life in the Far West
    - California gold diggers march Boston: Henry Tolman,[1848 -1852] (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Composed by Dr. H. G. Barrus
    - California polka New York: William Hall & Son,1849 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Composed by Miss Julia W. Pomeroy
    - Westward Ho: a favorite song and chorus Philadelphia: Klemm & Brother,1839 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Composed by M. Richter
    - California as it is: comic song New York: William Hall & Son,1849 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Written by Thaddeus W. Meighan
      Lithographer: Oliver & Brother, New York
      Performed by Pete Morris
    - To the west, to the west! [London]: Musical Bouquet ,n.d. (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Written by Charles Mackay, L.L.D.
      Lithographer: Mayall
      Performed by Henry Russell
      The Emigrant's Progress
    - California march Louisville: Peters, Webb & Co.,1849.Cincinnati: Peters & Field ,1849 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Composed by William Iucho
      Also published by W. C. Peters, New York
  - Subseries c. 1870 - 1879, Non-Illustrated
    - La chatelaine San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1870s] (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Music by A. le Duc
      Sherman & Hyde's collection of choice piano pieces
    - Let me dream again San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,[1876 -1878].San Jose: A. Waldteufel ,[1876 -1878] (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Music by Arthur Sullivan
      Words by B. C. Stephenson
      Arion collection of favorite songs
    - No, no I never can forget: ballad, answer to the composer's popular song 'The day when you'll forget me' San Francisco and Portland: Grays Music Stores,1872 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Music by J. R. Loomis
      Words by Pascal Loomis
    - Al fin brillar (At length with joy): valse San Francisco and Portland: Gray's Music Stores,1872 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Music by L. Ricci
      Translated and Arranged by H. Millard
      Fiori d'Italia: a Collection of Gems
    - I love you, you rogue: the celebrated dungeon song from Offenbach's La Perichole San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1876.New York: William A. Pond & Co. ,1876 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Music by Offenbach
      Performed by Miss Emily Melville
      Also published by A. Waldteufel, San Jose; O. Ditson & Co., Boston; and F. A. North & co., Philadelphia.
    - Angiol di pace (Angel of peace): terzettino San Francisco and Portland: Gray's Music Stores,1873 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Music by Bellini
    - A. A. Rosenberg, no. 139 Kearny Street, Cor. Sutton, San Francisco. Music Publisher and dealer in musical merchandise of every discreption, importer of pianos, parlor organs and melodeons. Agent for the celebrated Dunham & Sons, and Calenberg, Vaupel & Co's piano fortes. Church and Sabbath School Singing Books s.l..: s.d.,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Printer Spaulding & Barto, Music Printers, San Francisco
      Broadside only.
    - The sultan's polka San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Music by Charles d'Albert
      Happy hours choice selections from favorite authors
    - Overture to poet and peasant (Dichter und Bauer) San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Composed by Suppé
      Arranged by C. T. Brunner
    - Pretty as a picture schottische San Francisco: Sherman, Hyde & Co. ,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Arranged by Leonard Georges
    - New half and half polka San Francisco: A. A. Rosenberg,n.d.Sacramento: L. K. Hammer ,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Lithographer: Russell Bros., New York
      Also published by Geo. H. Hare, San Jose and Hillman & Co., Portland.
    - New half and half polka San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1871 -1877].Sacramento: L. K. Hammer ,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Pretty as a picture schottische San Francisco: McCurrie & Weber,1876 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - There's a letter in the candle: song and chorus San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Music by George T. Evans
    - Would you answer yes or no? San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1875 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Music by Charles E. Pratt
      Words by George Cooper
    - The sun flower schottische (with introduction) San Francisco: Gray's Music Store,1868 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Arranged by George T. Evans
    - Te deum laudamus San Francisco: M. Gray,1873 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      From :Episcopal Church music
    - Guild schottische San Francisco: James S. Smith,1876 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Composed by H. S. Krouse
    - The angel bride San Francisco: Charles S. Eaton,1875 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Music by S. N. Helmers
    - Tremolo, ràverie San Francisco: M. Gray,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Music by H. Rosellen
      From :Morceaux favoris pour le piano
    - Faust de Ch. Gounod San Francisco: M. Gray,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Arranged by D. Krug
      From :Fleurs melodiques: simple and instructive selections from favorite operas
    - The palace of truth: polka mazurka San Francisco: M. Gray,1872 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Music by Charles Schultz
      Performed by Mme. Erminie Venturoli
    - The swallow San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,[1876 -1878].San Jose: A. Waldteufel ,[1876 -1878] (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Music by Ciro Pensuti
    - Starry night for a ramble: song and chorus San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1871 -1878] (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Music by Samuel Bagnal
    - Mother says I mustn't San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1872 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Bright star of hope, or, Call me thine own San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Music by Halevy
      From :Beauties of German song
    - Baby mine: song and chorus San Francisco: California Music Publishing Company,1878 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Arranged by William W. Barbour
      Performed by Mr. T. B. Dixon
    - Unforgotten: beautiful song San Francisco: Bancroft, Knight & Co.,1879 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Speak to me! San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,n.d.San Jose: A. Waldteufel ,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Music by Fabio Campana
      Written by H. B. Farnie
      From :Flowers
    - The Danube river San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1878 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Music by Hamilton Aidé
      From :The Vocalist: choice songs, ballads, etc.
    - The bridge San Francisco: M. Gray,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Composed by Miss M. Lindsay
      Written by H. W. Longfellow, Esq.
      From :Vocal Beauties of England and America for Voice and Piano
    - Home memories San Francisco: M. Gray,1873 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Music by Charles Bray
      Words by W. R. Fortier
      From :The guitarist's repertoire: a collection of songs & ballads arranged principally by Manuel Y. Ferrer
      Arranged for guitar by M. Y. Ferrer
    - Could you or would you: song sung by Fanchette in the opera 'Royal Middy' San Francisco: Geo. W. Hagans,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Music by Genee
      From :Songs and choruses from the opera of Royal Middy, rapturously encored
    - Gavotte circus Renz San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Composed by Hermann Fliege
    - Gavotte circus Renz San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1877 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Tra-la-la-loo schottisch San Francisco: McCurrie, Weber & Co.,1877.New York: William A. Pond & Co. ,1877 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Also published by O. Ditson & Co., Boston.
    - Tra-la-la-loo schottisch San Francisco, Portland, and Stockton: Matthias Gray,1877.San Jose: A. Waldteufel ,1877 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Arranged by H. S. Krouse
      Performed by Ballenberg's Band
    - La baladine San Francisco: William A. Frey,[1865 -1880] (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Music by C. B. Lysberg
      From :Choice gems of melody by favorite authors
    - Bruder Lustig Galop San Francisco: William A. Frey,[1865 -1880] (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Music by Ch[arles] Denstedt
      From :Musical gems: a choice selection of brilliant compositions by favorite authors
    - Guild schottische San Francisco: James S. Smith,1876 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Composed by Harry S. Krouse
    - Blue Danube waltzes San Francisco: William A. Frey,[1865 -1880] (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Composed by Johann Strauss
    - The bridge San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1871 -1878] (Box 10, Folder 8)
      From :Choice vocal melodies
    - I love my love: song and chorus San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1871 -1877] (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Music by C. Pinsuti
      Words by C. Mackay
    - Pigmy schottische San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1876 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Composed by J. H. Dohrmann
    - How he loves me best San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray, Publisher,[1871 -1872] (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Composed by Desmond L. Ryan
      Written by H. Saville Clarke
    - Golden state march San Francisco: W. B. MacKellar,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Music by Adam Geibel
    - Mine leedle Yawcob Strauss San Francisco: L. Von der Mehden,1878 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Music by L. Von der Mehden
      Words by Charles F. Adams
    - The galloping sleigh ride polka San Francisco: Blackmar & Davis,[1879] (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Composed by J. P. Ordway
    - The puzzled Dutchman: comic song San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1875 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Music by E. G. Regennas
    - Davy Crocket's motto San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1870s] (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - La harpe Eolienne San Francisco: M. Gray,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Music by Sydney Smith
    - First kiss: polka San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Performed by Ballenberg's orchestra
      From :Compositions of Louis Bodecker
    - Poor little snowflake San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1876 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Performed by Miss Daniel
      Cover only. Music inside is 'Oh! Have pity, I pray,' music by J. H. Dohrmann, words by J. Woodard, Esq.
    - Nobody knows as I know: ballad San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1874 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Music by Frederick Clay
    - Mother says I mustn't San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1872 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Of what is the old man thinking?: old English words to a popular Spanish melody San Francisco: M. Gray,1878.San Jose: A. Waldteufel ,1878 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Adapted by George Hunt
      English words by J. H. Bayly
    - The summer time that was San Francisco: M. Gray,1871 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Composed by Oscar Weil
      Words by Owen Meredith
    - Fairest of the fair polka Santa Clara: E. C. E. Vile,1872.San Francisco: C. Eaton ,1872 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Music by E. C. E. Vile
      Printer College Press, Santa Clara; Spaulding & Barto, San Francisco
      Also published by Morton & Co., San Jose.
    - Moet and Chandon: sequel to Champagne Charlie San Francisco: Gray's Music Store,1871 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Composed by George Leybourne
      Written by H. Hurrile
      Performed by C. Vivian, Emeline Zavistowski and others
    - Pigmy schottische San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1876 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Weber polka for the piano forte San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1874.San Jose: Morton & Co. ,1874 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Composed by Leonard Georges
      Also published by Willaim Kierski, Stockton.
    - Palace of truth polka mazurka San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1872 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Lullaby schottische San Francisco: William A. Frey,1878 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Arranged by H. von der Mehden
    - Ivy Club lancers San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - La fille de Mme. Angot: opera comique San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,[1876] (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Oh! Don't we cut a dash!: schottische San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Grand march to the sunset land San Francisco: Charles S. Eaton,1870 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Composed by Albert I. Sumner
    - Annabel Lee: Ballad San Francisco: A. A. Rosenberg,1870.Sacramento: L. K. Hammer ,1870 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Composed by Jane W. Bruner
      Lithographer: Stackpole, New York
      Also published by G. W. Hillman, Portland; Henry Wagner, Marysville; and W. Brodrick, Los Angeles.
    - Dream thou of me, darling: ballad San Francisco: M. Gray,1870 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Written and composed by David Nesfield
    - When my ship comes in: schottische San Francisco: Sherman, Hyde, & Co.,1877 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Performed by Ballenberg's Orchestra
    - The dearest spot on Earth is home (Sweet home): transcription San Francisco and Portland: Gray's Music Stores,1872 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Music by W. T. Wrighton
      Arranged by Brinley Richards
    - Open the door: song and chorus San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1872 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Composed by Stephen Massett
    - The bridal schottische San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1875 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Composed by S. H. Marsh
    - Bright star of hope, or, Call me thine own San Francisco: M. Gray,1873.San Jose: A. Waldteufel ,1873 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Flute or violin ad lib by George Koppitz
      From :Dramma Musicale
    - Speak to me: ballad San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1871 -1878] (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Words by H. B. Farnie
    - Wm. A. Frey, publisher and dealer in foreign and American sheet music, music books, roman strings, pianos, organs, melodeons, violins, guitars, accordeons, and every description of musical merchandise, fancy goods, toilet articles, toys, etc., special attention given to the tuning & repairing of musical instruments all work warrantied. Sheet music arranged and neatly bound, orders from the country promptly attended to. All of the new music received as soon as published. Music sent by mail, prepaid, to any part of the coutnry, upon receipt of the Marked price. San Francisco: Wm. A. Frey,[1865 -1880] (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - The palace of truth: polka mazurka San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1872 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - When my ship comes in: schottische San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1877 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - The Aldine schottische San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1875 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Composed by Abe. Seeligsohn
    - Good night: ballad San Francisco, Portland, and Stockton: Matthias Gray,1877 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Music by Geoffrey C. Herbert
      Words by Rev. G. J. Flanders
    - Floretta schottische San Francisco: Sherman, Hyde & Co.,1877 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Composed by Adolph Pferdner
    - Herzberg galop San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde ,[1871 -1877] (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Composed by W. B. Elliot, Jr.
      From :Galops by favorite composers
    - Spider to the fly San Francisco: McCurrie & Weber,1875 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Transcription by A. A. Rosenberg
    - Dolly Hayes ballad San Francisco: T. J. Donnelly,n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Music by P. R. Nicholls
      Written by T. J. Donnelly
    - Courting San Francisco: M. Gray,1874 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Music by A. H. Pease
      Words by Anonymous
    - By the river: ballad San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1875 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Composed by Felix Marti
      Words by T. A. Kermode
    - Wedding march San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,n.d. (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Composed by F. Mendelssohn Bartholdy
      From :Perles musicales pour piano
    - Peri waltzes San Francisco: A. L. Bancroft & Co.,n.d. (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Music by Charles D'Albert
    - Il bacio waltz (The kiss) San Francisco: M. Gray,1871 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Music by Luigi Arditi
      From :Dance music for the piano
    - Courtland waltz San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1871 -1877] (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Music by Albert B. Cheney
    - I cannot tell you why: comic song for ladies with chorus San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1871 .New York: J. L. Peters ,1871 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Music by George W. Persley
      Words by Hank Darley
      Also published by Dobmeyer & Cody, Cincinnati; T. Goggan & Bro., Galveston; White, Smith, & Perry, Boston; and L. Grunewald, New Orleans.
    - My Gal! schottische San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1874 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Pretty as a picture schottische San Francisco: William A. Frey,1876.Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co. ,1876 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Pretty as a picture schottische San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1876.Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co. ,1876 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Baby mine schottische San Francisco: Matthias Gray,1878 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Pull down the blind San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,[1871 -1877] (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Words and Music by Charles McCarthy
      Arranged by J. Holmes
    - When the stars begin to peep schottische San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - When the stars begin to peep schottische San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Darling little Jessie: song and chorus San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1876 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Miss Lydia Thompson's song 'Silver on her heels' San Francisco: Gray's Music Store,1870 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - The wishing ring San Francisco and Porland: Gray's Music Stores,1874 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Composed by David Nesfield
      From :Gems of Song for Voice and Piano
    - I cannot sing the old songs: schottische San Francisco: William A. Frey,1878 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Music by W. Stuckenholz
    - Don't make a noise schottische San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1877 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Arranged by J. P. Meder
    - National song San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1876 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Music by John P. Morgan
      Words by Bayard Taylor
    - I'm waiting my darling for thee!: song and chorus San Francisco: M. Gray,1870 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Beautiful dreams of the twilight: song and chorus San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1876 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Is my darling true to me San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1875 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Performed by Alice Dunning
    - Lonely I wander, or, Rejected San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1874 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Music by G. H. Anderson
      Words by C. C. Haskins
    - I love the night San Jose: Morton & Co.,1875 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Composed by D. B. Moody
      Written by George P. Morris
    - Fairest of the fair: schottische San Francisco and Portland: Gray's Music Stores,1871 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Composed by G. L. De Prans
    - Hamlet mazourka San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray's Music Stores,1874 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Arranged by Charles E. Pratt
      From :Ambroise Thomas' celebrated opera 'Hamlet'
    - Arcadian march San Francisco: Kohler & Chase,1879 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Music by Harry S. Krouse
      Performed by Blum's Orchestra
    - When the stars begin to peep San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Performed by Maggie Moore
    - Sweet Emeline ballad San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1871 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Performed by Louis Braham
    - I cannot sing the old songs: schottische San Francisco: William A. Frey,1878 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - The days when I was young schottische San Francisco and Portland: Gray's Music Stores,1872 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Oh Nicodemus schottische San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1874.Philadelphia: Lee & Walker ,1874 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Music by H. M. Bosworth
    - Let those who quarrel fight San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1873 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Arranged by Henry Worth
      Performed by Maggie Moore and Billy Emerson
    - Ching Chow Chung: Chinese song and dance San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1872 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Over the way San Jose: A. Waldteufel,1876.San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray ,1876 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Music by D. B. Moody
      Poetry by Scribner's magazine
      From :Six songs of D. B. Moody
    - Waiting for the rain San Jose: A. Waldteufel,1875.San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray ,1875 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Written by Annie E. Fitzgerald
    - Kentucky Jubilee Singers' schottische, introducing the popular plantation melodies of 'Darkies on the levee,' 'Oh, Peter, go ring dem bells,' 'We'll cross de ribber ob Jordan,' and 'Swing low sweet chariot' San Francisco: A. L. Bancroft & Co.,1879 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Composed and Arranged by Frederick G. Carnes
    - Kentucky Jubilee Singers' schottische, introducing the popular plantation melodies of 'Darkies on the levee,' 'Oh, Peter, go ring dem bells,' 'We'll cross de ribber ob Jordan,' and 'Swing low sweet chariot' San Francisco: A. L. Bancroft & Co.,1879 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Stand me on my little head, a parody on 'Put me in my little bed': song and chorus San Francisco: Sherman & Hyde,1873 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Music by A. H. Rosewig
    - There's sunshine in the heart: song and chorus Philadelphia: F. A. North & Co.,1877 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Music by T. Brigham Bishop
      Words by Claude de Haven
      Lithographer: Thos. Hunter, Lith., Philadelphia
      From :Popular melodies of Emerson's California minstrels
    - You and I San Francisco: s.d.,[1873] (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Words and Music by Claribel
    - California, a grange song San Francisco: A. L. Bancroft & Co.,1875 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Music by Franz Abt
      Arranged by J. W. A. Wright
    - Guild schottische San Francisco: James S. Smith,1876 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - The Vivian medley San Francisco: Charles S. Eaton,1871 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - The palace of truth: polka mazurka San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray,1872 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - A knot of blue and gray: song Boston: Oliver Ditson & Co.,1876.New York: C. H. Ditson & Co. ,1876 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Jolly old Santa Claus San Jose: A. Waldteufel,1876.San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray ,1876 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Written by Sam Booth
      From :Six Songs by D. B. Moody
    - Night on the storm San Jose: A. Waldteufel,1876.San Francisco and Portland: M. Gray ,1876 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Poetry by Maria E. Sutherland